[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chanh mu\u043ei is a type of Vietnamese pickles. What is it made of?", "correct_answer": "Lime", "incorrect_answers": ["Bananas", "Papaya", "Grapefruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From our point of view on Earth, Mercury goes through different phases, just like our Moon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The custom of all bridesmaids dressing alike was started to ensure that bride would stand out and be the center of attention on the alter.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rabbi Levi and Rabbi Abraham ibn Ezra are places on the moon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1968 film starred Jane Fonda as a scantily-clad sci-fi heroine?", "correct_answer": "Barbarella", "incorrect_answers": ["Bambi Meets Godzilla", "Bandolero!", "Bullitt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where were the first windmills built?", "correct_answer": "Iran", "incorrect_answers": ["Peru", "Laos", "Tunisia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first automatic electric traffic light with 3 colors was installed in Detroit, Michigan in what year?", "correct_answer": "1920", "incorrect_answers": ["1885", "1850", "1942"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea?", "correct_answer": "Sicily", "incorrect_answers": ["Crete", "Corsica", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This female artists signature beehive hairdo is widely spoofed and copied.", "correct_answer": "Amy Winehouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Beyonce", "Janet Jackson", "Christina Aguilera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these continents is largest (by territory)?", "correct_answer": "North America", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Antarctica", "Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what geographic area is tooth filing practiced?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Philippines", "Africa", "Indonesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Oslo", "incorrect_answers": ["Stockholm", "Helsinki", "Copenhagen"]}]